Phase 1 budget is 1.2 billion
Third-party tech service fee is 160 million
The tech service fee ratio isn't low
Smart warehousing heavily relies on tech systems
This fee is a bit high
It's within the normal range
Your behavior now is also considered whistleblowing
60 million
1.65 to Lin Feixiang
Checking the budget, the stock price is 21.65
If it passes the preliminary review today
Next week the project will
enter the board for approval
Nangang's window is limited
We can't drag it out
Fu Group needs a stable signal right now
Chen Zhou just got back
And he needs a big project to establish himself
This isn't to let him get familiar with Fu Group
It's to force him to take a stand
What about you
I figured it out
And I've already found a lead
Chen Zhou's project is very important to Fu Group